<Root><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>5 Nights in Sunriver, Oregon!</name>
<desc>Enjoy 5 nights in a 1 bedroom condominium unit at The Pines, Sunriver, Oregon.  300 days of sun, world class golf, and the legendary Mt. Bachelor ski resort surround you with year round fun.  Paved bike trails, tennis courts, outdoor pool, hot tub and kids pool, sauna, exercise room, and arcade.  

Reservations may be scheduled up to ten (10) months in advance on a space available basis.</desc>
<value>$875</value>
<donor>Johnny &amp; Carol Flynn, Vacation Internationale</donor>
<id>77</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Team Signed Seattle Sounders Soccer Ball</name>
<desc>The ultimate must-have for your sports memorabilia collection! The entire 2010 Seattle Sounders team has autographed this soccer ball and you could be its proud owner!</desc>
<value>Priceless</value>
<donor>Seattle Sounders</donor>
<id>93</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Team Signed Seattle Sounders Soccer Ball</name>
<desc>The ultimate must-have for your sports memorabilia collection! The entire 2010 Seattle Sounders team has autographed this soccer ball and you could be its proud owner!</desc>
<value>Priceless</value>
<donor>Seattle Sounders</donor>
<id>94</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Week long Luxury Log Home Vacation in Central Oregon</name>
<desc>One week stay in a custom built Scandinavian scribed log home in Central Oregon--just 10 minutes from the Redmond, OR airport and 20 minutes from downtown Bend!  A gorgeous 4 bedroom, 3 bathroom home on 5 acres of mountain views!  Some custom features include river rock fireplace, hardwood floors, granite countertops, and huge windows for the views.  One hour from Mt. Bachelor, 20 minutes from Smith Rock, and rich golf options abound.</desc>
<value>$2,000</value>
<donor>Carri Coultas</donor>
<id>96</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>U2 Tickets for Four!!</name>
<desc>It's a beautiful day!  Here's your chance to see U2 live in concert in Seattle happening at Qwest Field on Sunday, June 20th at 7 pm.  Enjoy 4 tickets in Section 241, Row D, Seats 1-4.</desc>
<value>$380</value>
<donor>Joe &amp; Amy Cheng</donor>
<id>108</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>2 Seahawk Tickets and Pregame Sideline Passes</name>
<desc>Head down to Qwest Field to watch your Seattle Seahawks.  You and a guest will receive tickets to a 2010 Seahawks regular season game.  This great package will include a pregame sideline experience to watch player warm-ups from the sidelines.  Go Seahawks!</desc>
<value>$250</value>
<donor>Seattle Seahawks</donor>
<id>126</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>2 Sounders FC tickets with Pregame Sideline Passes</name>
<desc>Head down to the XBOX Pitch at Qwest Field to watch the Sounders FC!  You and a guest will receive tickets to a 2010 Sounders FC regular season match.  Scarves Up!</desc>
<value>$125</value>
<donor>Seattle Sounders</donor>
<id>128</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Perfect Puppy Package</name>
<desc>Take home this precious Puggle Puppy today! Puggles are a designer breed between a pug father and a beagle mother. This puppy will weigh around 15 to 20 pounds as an adult. Puggles make wonderful family companions and they are great with children. This sweet guy has had his first and second set of shots. He will make a great addition to any family.

Care for your new pup with a holistic exam for your pet with Dr. Tejinder Sodhi or Dr. Raja Velu at the Animal Wellness and Rehab Center, Bellevue. 

PLUS - You get a $50 Gift Card to Denny's Pet World. Located in the Totem Lake Shopping Center, Denny's Pet World has a complete selection of products for your pet as well as animals &amp; fish for purchase.</desc>
<value>$850</value>
<donor>Animal Wellness and Rehab Center, Paula Cox, Kelley Parsons</donor>
<id>142</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>The Ultimate Home Improvement Package: Design, Contracting and Cleaning</name>
<desc>Architectual Design: Five hours of design consultation from architect David Gilchrist.  Let him put his residential and commercial experience to work for you and take the first step toward making your dream a reality!  

Another Certificate entitles you to 8 hours of Mike Nelson Contracting's Labor including repairs, remodel of kitchens and baths, light plumbing repairs or replacement, water damage repair and consultations. 

Are you thinking of redecorating and need some professional advise? Maybe you just want a fresh new look for your room using what you already have.  Let the interior designers at Masin's Furniture &amp; Interior Design make your space everything you'd hope it could be with: Space Planning, Furnishings, Art, Accessories, Rugs, Window Treatments, Color Consultation 

As if you needed more - see why Mrs. Clean has been cleaning houses since 1975! Call Mrs. Clean for the best house cleaning services you can get. They bring all the cleaning supplies and equipment to tackle your toughest cleaning job, and leave your home or office bright and shining clean.
The maids at Mrs.Clean will clean it right! They are:
&#8226;Licensed, Bonded &amp; Insured   &#8226;Background checked &amp; e-verified employees   &#8226;Subcontractors never used   &#8226;Fully trained staff   &#8226;Reliable, flexible scheduling   &#8226;Regular or one-time cleaning   &#8226;Move-in/move-out cleaning   &#8226;Customized cleaning services available   &#8226;All employee taxes &amp; insurance paid   &#8226;Residential, home, office, condo, apt, commercial cleaning   &#8226;Fussy clients welcomed   &#8226;Will use any green cleaning products you provide 

To top this package off, you will receive $150 toward gutter cleaning from Master Butler. 

Take advantage of this FABULOUS package that will make all members of the household smile! + Sit back and enjoy having someone else do the job! Professional services of Green Flash Yard Maintenance.
Mow, edge, blow and general yard cleanup.</desc>
<value>$2,026</value>
<donor>David Gilchrist Architect, Robert Long, Masins Furniture &amp; Interior Design, Master Butler, Mrs.Clean USA Professional Cleaning Service, Inc, Nelson Contracting</donor>
<id>145</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Obadiah Day of Beauty &amp; Relaxation</name>
<desc>Have the most amazing day of your year after enjoying:

One Classic Facial with Chrissy
One Hour Massage with Gina
One Manicure &amp; Pedicure with Marisa
One Haircut with Nathan</desc>
<value>$315</value>
<donor></donor>
<id>155</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Ultimate Woodinville Wine Experience</name>
<desc>Complimentary wine tasting for 6 guests with 3 gourmet flatbread pizzas at the Columbia Winery, Woodinville. + This card entitles you to a one-time 30% discount on a wine purchase of your choice at Columbia Winery, Woodinville. + 3 Columbia Valley Tastes at Novelty Hill/Januik Winery for 6 and 3 pizza's.</desc>
<value>$312</value>
<donor>Columbia Winery, De Lille Cellars, Blane Lacroix-Ball</donor>
<id>159</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Ultimate Yoga Rejuvination Package</name>
<desc>Gift certificate for $100 towards service of choice at Allure Facial Laser Center and Medispa.  Allure specialized in procedures of the eyes and rejuvenation of the skin and body to enhance your appearance. + This package includes a one-year membership at Fusion Hot Yoga, an aluminum water bottle, and a yoga mat.  Fusion Hot Yoga offers Hatha yoga, Power Vinyasa yoga, and our new intense Fusion signature series all in a state-of-the-art climate-controlled heated room.  The Fusion series combines the benefits of yoga and resistance training into one powerful yogic experience!  Located in Bothell. + NaLa Seattle's newest Spring Collection to take you from the gym throughout your day in comfort and style.  Come away with a new workout wardrobe including the following styles:

Twist it Sister Tank
Shake that Thang Capri</desc>
<value>$1,268</value>
<donor>Allure Facial Laser Center &amp; Medispa, Fusion Hot Yoga, NaLa Seattle</donor>
<id>161</id>
</item><item><image href=""/>
<tag>L</tag>
<name>Bill the Butcher's Natural Wagyu Prime Rib Roast Dinner for 8</name>
<desc>Enjoy and amazing meal with friends! Feast on Bill the Butcher's Heavenly Natural Wagyu Prime Rib Roast Dinner. Butcher and Executive Chef Scott Molyneaux will come to a private event at your home and prepare their famously exceptional Wagyu Prime Rib Roast for your party of eight.  Wagyu is the American version of Kobe beef and is unsurpassed in its flavor, tenderness and juiciness.  This is sure to be an event and a meal to remember.

This package also includes SIX $25 In-Store Gift Certificates.</desc>
<value>$700</value>
<donor>Bill the Butcher</donor>
<id>170</id>
</item></Root>